//creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Near a pedestrian crossing, when the pedestrians are waiting to cross the road, you should",
    answer: "Stop the vehicle and wait till the pedestrians cross the road and then proceed",
    options: [
      "Stop the vehicle and wait till the pedestrians cross the road and then proceed",
      "Slow down, sound horn and pass",
      "Sound horn and proceed",
      "Stop and take u-turn"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question:"Driver of a vehicle may overtake",
    answer: "When the driver of the vehicle in front shows the signal tob overtake",
    options: [
      "When the driver of the vehicle in front shows the signal tob overtake",
      "while driving downhill",
      "If the road is sufficiently wide",
      "If it is right side of the road"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "When an ambulance is approaching ..",
    answer: "the driver shall allow free passage by drawing to the side of the road",
    options: [
      "no preference need be given.",
      "allow passage if there are no vehicles from front side.",
      "the driver shall allow free passage by drawing to the side of the road",
      "Do not allow to overtake"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Parking a vehicle in front of entrance to hospital",
    answer: "improper",
    options: [
      "proper",
      "Proper if no parking sign is not provided",
      "improper",
      "allowed if the vehicle is of doctors",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "On a one-way road, you should not?",
    answer: "Drive in the reverse gear",
    options: [
      "Over-speed",
      "Park on the way",
      "Drive in the reverse gear",
      "Honk a lot"
    ]
  },
 
    {
     numb:6 ,
     question: "How do you know that a vehicle is a transport vehicle?",
     answer: "By seeing the number plate of the vehicle",
     options: [
       "By the make of the vehicle",
       "By the driverâ€™s license",
       "By seeing the number plate of the vehicle",
	   "None of this",
     ]
   },
   
   {
     numb: 7,
     question: "Overtaking is allowed only:",
     answer: "From the right side",
     options: [
       "From the right side",
       "From the left side",
       "After honking 3 times  ",
	   "All of above",
       
     ]
   },
   {
     numb:8,
     question: "While travelling uphill which vehicle has the right-of-way over others? ,question: ",
     answer: "Any vehicle travelling uphill",
     options: [
       "Largest vehicle",
       "Longest vehicle",
       "Any vehicle travelling uphill",
       "The vehicle which came firsts",
	 
    ]
   },
   {
     numb: 9,
     question: "Overtaking will be forbidden in case",
     answer: "All mentioned as above",
     options: [
       "Roads look greasy",
       "Dangerous to approaching traffic",
       "All mentioned as above",
	    "None of this",
       
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 10,
     question: "Red signal in traffic implies:",
     answer: "Please stop your vehicle",
     options: [
       "Please slow down your vehicle",
       "Move with caution",
       "Please stop your vehicle",
        "None of this",
     ]
   },
   
];